const quiz2data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "The film wasn't very good, but I liked __ music.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ''
   },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "__ life has changed a lot in the last thirty years.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "the", isCorrect: false},
      ]
   },
  //   {
  //     id: 3,
  //     question: "All __ cars in this car belong to people who work here.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 4,
  //     question: "I took a taxi to __ station.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 5,
  //     question: "__ giraffe is my favorite animal.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "The", isCorrect: true},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 6,
  //     question: "__ Greek people are very friendly.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "The", isCorrect: false},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 7,
  //     question: "I went to __ university to meet Professor Thomas.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 8,
  //     question: "Can you turn off __ television, please?",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 9,
  //     question: "__ internet has changed the way we live.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "The", isCorrect: true},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 10,
  //     question: "I go to __ cinema a lot, but I haven't been to the theatre for ages.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: false},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 11,
  //     question: "Our train leaves from __ platform 5.",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: false},
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
  //     ]
  //  },
  //   {
  //     id: 12,
  //     question: "What time do you usually finish __ work?",
  //     answersList: [
  //       {answer: "-", isCorrect: true},
  //       {answer: "the", isCorrect: false},
  //     ]
  //  },
  ]
export default quiz2data
